Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
(Bed 26-29)
(السرير26-29)
Have you been waiting long?
هل انتظرت طويلاً؟
I just got here.
لقد وصلت للتو إلى هنا.
Have you figured out how to handle the shareholders' meeting?
هل اكتشفت كيفية التعامل مع اجتماع المساهمين؟
Uncle Zhaohui has Shen Tingyuan backing him.
العم Zhaohui لديه Shen Tingyuan دعمه.
But now I have you.
ولكن الآن لدي لك.
Besides,
علاوة على ذلك
I plan to use a new strategic investment agreement
أخطط لاستخدام جديد اتفاقية استثمار استراتيجي
during the voting session.
خلال جلسة التصويت.
Wanxin,
وانكسين،
why do you think
لماذا تعتقد
they never considered you as acting chairperson?
لم يعتبروك أبدًا كرئيس بالنيابة؟
Because I'm adopted by Grandfather and Dad.
لأنني متبني بواسطة الجد والأب.
Don't worry. Go ahead with your plan.
لا تقلق. المضي قدما في خطتك.
I'll take care of your grandfather.
سأعتني بجدك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=أصداء مدينة العصابة=
=Episode 3= (Love Lifts Us Higher)
=الحلقة 3= (الحب يرفعنا إلى أعلى)
CEO Xu Zhaoming of Minghui Group has suddenly passed away.
الرئيس التنفيذي Xu Zhaoming لمجموعة Minghui لقد توفي فجأة.
(In Memory of Mr. Xu Zhaoming) Chairman Xu Qianmo remains seriously ill,
(تخليداً لذكرى السيد شو تشاومينغ) لا يزال الرئيس Xu Qianmo مريضًا بشكل خطير،
and the stock continues to fall.
ويستمر السهم في الانخفاض.
A shareholders' meeting is being held today to elect an acting chairperson.
سيتم عقد اجتماع المساهمين اليوم لانتخاب رئيس بالنيابة.
According to predictions,
حسب التوقعات
Xu Zhaohui, the son of Chairman Xu Qianmo,
شو تشاوهوي، نجل الرئيس شو كيانمو
(Minghui Group) is the most likely successor.
(مجموعة مينغوي) هو الوريث الأكثر احتمالا.
Uncle Zhaohui.
العم تشاوهوي.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Shouldn't you
ألا ينبغي لك
be with your grandfather?
تكون مع جدك؟
I can handle this.
أستطيع التعامل مع هذا.
I've asked Xi to take care of him.
لقد طلبت من شي أن يعتني به.
I just came to see
لقد جئت للتو لأرى
if there's anything I can help with.
إذا كان هناك أي شيء يمكنني المساعدة به.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.
Today's agenda is to elect an acting chairperson.
جدول أعمال اليوم هو انتخاب رئيس بالنيابة.
The candidates are
المرشحين هم
Mr. Xu Zhaohui
السيد شو تشاوهوي
and
و
Ms. Xu Wanxin.
السيدة شو وانكسين.
Wait.
انتظر.
Is this a mistake?
هل هذا خطأ؟
Wanxin is about to marry Shen Hao.
Wanxin على وشك الزواج من Shen Hao.
Is it appropriate for her
فهل يليق بها
to interfere
للتدخل
in the family business now?
في الشركات العائلية الآن؟
Mr. Hui,
السيد هوي،
I don't think Wanxin should accept
لا أعتقد أن وانكسين يجب أن يقبل
a harsh marriage arrangement like that.
ترتيب زواج قاسي من هذا القبيل.
That would only push Minghui
هذا من شأنه أن يدفع Minghui فقط
toward being taken over.
نحو الاستيلاء عليها.
So it seems
هكذا يبدو
Miss Xu
ملكة جمال شو
is unwilling to marry Shen Hao
غير راغب في الزواج من شين هاو
for the sake of Minghui.
من أجل Minghui.
Wanxin,
وانكسين،
I've always thought
لقد اعتقدت دائما
Shen Hao and you would make a good match.
شين هاو وأنت من شأنه أن يقدم مباراة جيدة.
Junlin Group's support
دعم مجموعة جونلين
is crucial to us right now.
أمر بالغ الأهمية بالنسبة لنا في الوقت الحالي.
Of course,
بالطبع
if you don't want to marry Shen Hao,
إذا كنت لا تريد الزواج من شين هاو،
I won't force you
لن أجبرك
to sacrifice your marriage
للتضحية بزواجك
for the family.
للعائلة.
I'll sell
سأبيع
and mortgage
والرهن العقاري
all my assets
كل أصولي
to secure Junlin's help
لتأمين مساعدة Junlin
and get us through this crisis.
وإخراجنا من هذه الأزمة.
I won't let anyone
لن أسمح لأحد
laugh at Minghui.
اضحك على مينغوي.
Uncle Zhaohui,
العم تشاوهوي،
I never said
أنا لم أقل
I would cancel the marriage alliance with Junlin Group.
سأقوم بإلغاء تحالف الزواج مع مجموعة جونلين.
I've already married
لقد تزوجت بالفعل
its largest shareholder,
أكبر مساهم فيها
Shen Gu.
شين جو.
Xu Wanxin,
شو وانكسين،
you're unbelievable!
أنت لا تصدق!
Even if you're not marrying Shen Hao,
حتى لو لم تتزوجي من شين هاو،
since when does your marriage get to be decided by you alone?
منذ متى زواجك هل ستقرر أنت وحدك؟
Marrying Shen Gu?
الزواج من شين جو؟
What can he offer us?
ماذا يمكن أن يقدم لنا؟
Where's Miss Xu?
أين الآنسة شو؟
We need a family member to sign this.
نحن بحاجة إلى أحد أفراد الأسرة للتوقيع على هذا.
Please give it to me.
من فضلك أعطها لي.
You are?
أنت؟
(Groom: Shen Gu, Bride: Xu Wanxin)
(العريس: شين جو، العروس: شو وانكسين)
Shen Gu.
شين جو.
My apologies
اعتذاري
for being late.
لتأخره.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
That's Fang Hongsheng,
هذا فانغ هونغ شنغ،
son of Lawyer Fang and the daughter of Chen's Bank.
ابن المحامي فانغ وابنة بنك تشين.
Young Master Fang,
السيد الشاب فانغ،
this is Minghui's shareholders' meeting.
هذا اجتماع المساهمين في Minghui.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Don't call me that.
لا تدعوني بذلك.
I'm Mr. Shen Gu's legal director and CFO,
أنا السيد شين جو المدير القانوني والمدير المالي،
Fang Hongsheng.
فانغ هونغ شنغ.
I'm here today
أنا هنا اليوم
on behalf of Mr. Shen Gu
نيابة عن السيد شين جو
to announce a partnership with Minghui Group.
للإعلان عن الشراكة مع مجموعة Minghui.
A partnership?
شراكة؟
What kind?
أي نوع؟
The contract I hold
العقد الذي أحمله
was signed between Ms. Xu Wanxin and Mr. Shen Gu.
تم التوقيع بين السيدة Xu Wanxin والسيد Shen Gu.
Mr. Shen has committed
لقد التزم السيد شين
that if Minghui's stock falls to the point
أنه إذا كان مخزون Minghui يقع على النقطة
where bank loans must be repaid,
حيث يجب سداد القروض البنكية،
we'll mortgage all Junlin shares we have
سنقوم برهن جميع أسهم Junlin التي لدينا
to help Minghui settle its debts
لمساعدة Minghui في تسوية ديونها
and stand with Minghui Group through it all.
والوقوف مع مجموعة Minghui من خلال كل ذلك.
May I ask,
هل لي أن أسأل
Young Master Xu,
السيد الشاب شو،
can Shen Tingyuan
يمكن شين تينغ يوان
offer the same?
تقدم نفس؟
(Cooperation and Share Guarantee Agreement)
(التعاون واتفاقية ضمان الأسهم)
(Key Commitment Terms)
(شروط الالتزام الرئيسية)
What a clever niece I have.
يا لها من ابنة أخت ذكية.
You know how to work behind the scenes.
أنت تعرف كيفية العمل خلف الكواليس.
Whatever Shen Gu can give you,
كل ما يمكن أن يقدمه لك Shen Gu،
I can find a way to match.
يمكنني أن أجد طريقة للمطابقة.
But you,
لكن أنت
after all these years using the Xu family name,
بعد كل هذه السنوات باستخدام اسم عائلة Xu،
do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
you're one of us?
هل أنت واحد منا؟
Everyone,
الجميع،
Xu Wanxin
شو وانكسين
is my elder brother's adopted daughter.
هي ابنة أخي الأكبر بالتبني.
She
هي
has no inheritance rights.
ليس لديه حقوق الميراث.
(Adoption Certificate)
(شهادة التبني)
Two years ago,
منذ عامين،
due to a major mistake you made,
بسبب خطأ فادح ارتكبته،
the company suffered a great loss.
تكبدت الشركة خسارة كبيرة.
You were forced to leave the board.
لقد اضطررت لترك المجلس.
My dad,
والدي
Mr. Xu Zhaoming took over all operations.
السيد شو تشاومينغ تولى جميع العمليات.
Grandfather had the will notarized.
وكان الجد وصية موثقة.
It clearly states
ينص بوضوح على
the share distribution
توزيع الاسهم
for every member
لكل عضو
of the Xu family.
من عائلة شو.
(Signed by the Testator, Xu Zhaoming)
(توقيع الموصي شو تشاومينغ)
There's more good news.
هناك المزيد من الأخبار الجيدة.
Before my dad's passing, he secured an investment deal
قبل رحيل والدي، حصل على صفقة استثمارية
with a major company.
مع شركة كبرى.
Investment?
استثمار؟
Why don't I know about this?
لماذا لا أعرف عن هذا؟
Because I'm the designated contact.
لأنني جهة الاتصال المعينة.
Due to confidentiality,
نظراً للسرية،
I can only say
لا يسعني إلا أن أقول
the funds have been transferred.
تم تحويل الأموال.
Check if you don't believe me.
تحقق مما إذا كنت لا تصدقني.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I'd like to confirm
أود التأكيد
if any new capital has come in.
إذا تم وصول أي رأس مال جديد.
One moment. Let me check.
لحظة واحدة. اسمحوا لي أن التحقق.
Yes, the funds have just been received.
نعم، لقد تم استلام الأموال للتو.
To stabilize Minghui's stock price,
لتحقيق استقرار سعر سهم Minghui،
I will
سأفعل
hold a press conference as acting chairperson.
عقد مؤتمر صحفي كرئيس بالنيابة.
As the largest shareholder of Junlin Group, Shen Gu will make a statement.
باعتبارها أكبر مساهم في مجموعة Junlin، سوف يدلي شين غو ببيان.
It went well.
سارت الأمور بشكل جيد.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Don't worry about the press conference tomorrow.
لا تقلق بشأن المؤتمر الصحفي غدا .
This time,
هذه المرة
I'm going to drive the knife into Shen Tingyuan.
انا ذاهب لقيادة السكين في شين تينغ يوان.
No.
رقم
I'm going to stab it right into his heart.
انا ذاهب لطعنه الحق في قلبه.
Three days.
ثلاثة أيام.
Shen Gu has only been back for three days.
لقد عاد Shen Gu للتو لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
First, he calls a shareholder's meeting
أولاً، يدعو إلى اجتماع المساهمين
and throws our board into chaos.
ويلقي مجلسنا في حالة من الفوضى.
Then he gets close to Xu Wanxin without us realizing it,
ثم يقترب من Xu Wanxin دون أن ندرك،
and they're married.
وهم متزوجون.
Now they're going to hold a press conference together.
الآن سوف يصمدون مؤتمر صحفي معا.
I'm still the chairman of Junlin Group.
ما زلت الرئيس من مجموعة جونلين.
He has no right to represent Junlin Group.
ليس له الحق لتمثيل مجموعة Junlin.
I don't care whether he represents the company or not.
لا يهمني سواء يمثل الشركة أم لا.
I look like a complete fool right now.
أنا أبدو مثل أحمق كامل الآن.
Eight years.
ثماني سنوات.
What does that make the eight years I spent with Xu Wanxin?
ماذا يعني ذلك أن السنوات الثماني قضيت مع شو وانكسين؟
Enough already!
يكفي بالفعل!
If you were any good,
لو كنت خيرا
you would've married Xu Wanxin yourself.
كنت ستتزوج من Xu Wanxin بنفسك.
She chose Shen Gu.
اختارت شين جو.
Then she'll have to bear the consequences.
ثم أنها سوف تضطر إلى ذلك تحمل العواقب.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Make it more convincing.
اجعلها أكثر إقناعا.
♪The clouds hide the faint light behind them♪
♪ الغيوم تخفي الضوء الخافت خلفهم ♪
♪A lonely bench on the street corner♪
♪ مقعد وحيد على زاوية الشارع ♪
♪Where all feelings come to rest♪
♪ حيث تستقر كل المشاعر ♪
♪In the night sky, the moon's trail♪
♪ في سماء الليل درب القمر ♪
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪ يُخيط ويهدئ حزني ♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪شجاعة التقرب منك♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪يبعد ترددي♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
♪يتقلب القدر ويجمعنا ♪
♪I search my memories with all my might♪
♪ أبحث في ذكرياتي بكل قوتي ♪
♪Love catches me off guard♪
♪ الحب يفاجئني ♪
♪You, in the album♪
♪أنت في الألبوم ♪
♪Shine through my past like starlight♪
♪ تألق في الماضي مثل ضوء النجوم ♪
♪You fall between light and shadow♪
♪ أنت تقع بين الضوء والظل ♪
♪Melting all my fears away♪
♪ ذوبان كل مخاوفي ♪
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪الليلة يتساقط المطر ناعمًا وبطيئًا♪
♪Blending with letters left unread drifting through the air♪
♪ مزج مع الحروف التي تركت غير مقروءة الانجراف في الهواء ♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪ استدر ونظر إليّ ♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears quietly appear♪
♪ في تلك العيون نفسها دموع مألوفة تظهر بهدوء ♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪ يبدو الأمر وكأننا حملنا الكثير ♪
♪So many questions time itself could not make clear♪
♪الكثير من الأسئلة الوقت نفسه لا أستطيع التوضيح ♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪اللحظة التي دخلت فيها حياتي♪
♪Every dream I had became something I want with you near♪
♪ كل حلم حلمت به أصبح شيئًا أريد معك بالقرب ♪
♪How many letters have I written just for you?♪
♪ كم عدد الحروف لديها كتبت لأجلك فقط؟ ♪
♪If only you could truly hear what my heart is trying to say♪
♪ لو كنت تستطيع أن تسمع حقًا ما يحاول قلبي قوله ♪
♪From this life on no distance could keep us apart♪
♪ من هذه الحياة بلا مسافة يمكن أن يفرقنا ♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪ الوعد الذي قطعناه ♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled one day♪
♪ سوف تجد طريقها إلى الوفاء بها يوم واحد ♪
♪But I want more than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪لكنني أريد المزيد من مجرد تلك النظرة العابرة ♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪ ما زلت لم أسمع إجابتك ♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending we face?♪
♪هل لا يزال بإمكاننا إعادة كتابة النهاية نواجه؟ ♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you will hear it all♪
♪ عندما يبدأ الندم بالالتفاف حولك سوف نسمع كل شيء ♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪
♪ كل ما يعيدني إليك ♪